Good morning and good afternoon and welcome everyone to our Q2 2026 conference call.
The information presented today contains forward-looking statements that involve known
and unknown risks, uncertainties and other factors. These may cause actual results to
be materially different from any future results, performance or achievements expressed or implied
by such statements. For a description of some of these factors, please refer to the company's
Form 20F and its most recent quarterly results on Form 6K that respectively were filed with
and furnished to the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission. Before we get started and as a
reminder, please kindly limit yourselves to one question at a time and we'll cycle through the
queue as needed. And with that, I'll hand over to Vaz. Thank you, Nigel. Thanks everyone for joining
today's conference call. Moving to slide four, as you saw in the results released earlier today,
Novartis delivered strong performance.
Across our priority brands and launches while advancing the pipeline, allowing us to return
to growth in the second quarter. The business grew 1% in constant currencies in USD and we
had flat core operating income at $5.9 billion. Mukul will go through the numbers in more detail
later on in the call, but we're reaffirming our full year guidance for 2026. We also had some
important pipeline highlights, which I'll talk about more during the course of the conference
call.
Including updated Qiskali OS data, the Delbrax biomarker data in FSHD, as well as some other
regulatory milestones we were able to deliver over the course of the quarter.
Now moving to slide five, our growth drivers continued a strong trajectory in quarter two.
They were up 36% in constant currencies. Some of the highlights include strong performance from
Qiskali, Casimta, Semblix, solid performance from Pluvicto, and strong performance as well from
Lectio. So overall taken together, these growth drivers are performing strongly. We believe that
gives us momentum going into the second quarter, second half of the year, as we now move beyond the
Entrusto patent expiry and set us up well to deliver on our midterm growth guidance.
Now moving to slide six, Qiskali was up 43% in constant currencies on the quarter,
we outpaced the CDK 4.6 market with strong performance in the US and outside the US.
In the US, we were up 39% reaching over a billion dollars in sales for the first time. We